[{
    "id": "0",
    "question": "What's the name of the spell that unlocks doors?",
    "options": [
        "Alchemy",
        "Alohomora",
        "Open Sesame",
        "Apparate"
    ],
    "correct": "Alohomora"
},
{
    "id": "1",
    "question": "What's the name of the spell that causes immense pain?",
    "options": [
        "Crucio",
        "Cruel",
        "Inflicto",
        "Incarcarous"
    ],
    "correct": "Crucio"

},
{
    "id": "2",
    "question": "What's the name of the spell that stuns your opponent?",
    "options": [
        "Impirium",
        "Stupefy",
        "Stunned",
        "Silencio"
    ],
    "correct": "Stupefy"

},
{
    "id": "3",
    "question": "What's the name of the spell that makes objects explode?",
    "options": [
        "Boom",
        "Explodiosous",
        "Reducio",
        "Reducto"
    ],
    "correct": "Reducto"

},
{
    "id": "4",
    "question": "What's the name of the spell that illuminates the tip of your wand?",
    "options": [
        "Lox",
        "Lumos",
        "Imperio",
        "Clap On"
    ],
    "correct": "Lumos"

},
{
    "id": "5",
    "question": "What's the name of the spell that turns the illuminated wand tip off?",
    "options": [
        "Nox",
        "No",
        "Nought",
        "Clap Off"
    ],
    "correct": "Nox"

},
{
    "id": "6",
    "question": "What's the name of the spell that erases someone's memory?",
    "options": [
        "Oblivious",
        "Imperio",
        "Obliviate",
        "Incarcarous"
    ],
    "correct": "Obliviate"

},
{
    "id": "7",
    "question": "What's the name of the spell that creates fire?",
    "options": [
        "Incend",
        "Incendio",
        "Arsonino",
        "Matches"
    ],
    "correct": "Incendio"

},
{
    "id": "8",
    "question": "Which spell shoots out water?",
    "options": [
        "Aquamenta",
        "Aguamenti",
        "Geminio",
        "Anapneo"
    ],
    "correct": "Aguamenti"

},
{
    "id": "9",
    "question": "Which one is the disarming charm?",
    "options": [
        "Episkey",
        "Expelliarmus",
        "Expecto Patronum",
        "Expellediomus"
    ],
    "correct": "Expelliarmus"

},
{
    "id": "10",
    "question": "Which spell levitates objects?",
    "options": [
        "Wingardium Leviosa",
        "Impervius",
        "Levitato",
        "Let it fly!"
    ],
    "correct": "Wingardium Leviosa"

},
{
    "id": "11",
    "question": "Which one is the summoning spell?",
    "options": [
        "Asico",
        "Diffindo",
        "Descendo",
        "Accio"
    ],
    "correct": "Accio"

},
{
    "id": "12",
    "question": "What's the name of the spell that conjures the Patronus charm?",
    "options": [
        "Expecto Patronum",
        "Patronious",
        "Protego",
        "Riddikulus"
    ],
    "correct": "Expecto Patronum"

},
{
    "id": "13",
    "question": "What is the curse that locks someone's legs?",
    "options": [
        "Impedimenta",
        "Locomotor Mortis",
        "Piertotum Locomotor",
        "Locomotora Legs"
    ],
    "correct": "Locomotor Mortis"

},
{
    "id": "14",
    "question": "Which spell transforms a Boggart into something humorous?",
    "options": [
        "Riddikulus",
        "Ridiculous",
        "Reducio",
        "Expecto Patronum"
    ],
    "correct": "Riddikulus"

},
{
    "id": "15",
    "question": "What's the name of the spell that shrinks objects?",
    "options": [
        "Downsized",
        "Reducio",
        "Pack",
        "Prior Incantato"
    ],
    "correct": "Reducio"

},
{
    "id": "16",
    "question": "Which spell helps you clean things?",
    "options": [
        "Bubble Srubble",
        "Portus",
        "Scrubio",
        "Scourgify"
    ],
    "correct": "Scourgify"

},
{
    "id": "17",
    "question": "Which spell temporally creates a worthless duplicate of an object?",
    "options": [
        "Geminio",
        "Duplicato",
        "Obscuro",
        "Muliprano"
    ],
    "correct": "Geminio"

},
{
    "id": "18",
    "question": "Which spell makes your opponent paralyzed?",
    "options": [
        "Deletrius",
        "Petrificius Totalus",
        "Densaugeo",
        "Paralization"
    ],
    "correct": "Petrificius Totalus"

},
{
    "id": "19",
    "question": "What is the name of the killing spell?",
    "options": [
        "Abracadabra",
        "Anapneo",
        "Repelo Muggletum",
        "Avada Kedavra"
    ],
    "correct": "Avada Kedavra"

}	
]